export const Questions={
    Html:[
        {
            question:"HTML stands for -",
            options:["HighText Machine Language","HyperText and links Markup Language","HyperText Markup Language","None of these"],
            answer:"HyperText Markup Language"
        },
        {
            question:"Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",
            options:["<pre>","<a>","<b>","<br></br>"],
            answer:"<b>"
        },
        {
            question:"The <hr> tag in HTML is used for -",
            options:[" new line","vertical ruler","new paragraph","horizontal ruler"],
            answer:" horizontal ruler"
        },
        {
            question:"Who is the father of HTML?",
            options:["Rasmus Lerdorf","Tim Berners-Lee","Brendan Eich","Sergey Brin"],
            answer:"Tim Berners-Lee"
        },

    ],
    CSS:[
        {
            question:"The full form of CSS is:",
            options:["Cascade style sheets","Color and style sheets","Cascading style sheets","None of the above"],
            answer:"Cascading style sheets"
        },
        {
            question:"The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
            options:["bgcolor","color","background-color","All of the above"],
            answer:"background-color"
        },
        {
            question:"The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is -",
            options:["text-style","text-size","font-size","None of the above"],
            answer:" font-size"
        },
        {
            question:"The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is -",
            options:["style","styles","class","None of the above"],
            answer:"style"
        }

    ],
    Bootstrap:[
        {
            question:"Who developed the bootstrap?",
            options:["James Gosling","Mark Jukervich","Dennis Ritchie","Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton"],
            answer:"Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton" 
        },
        {
            question:"Is Bootstrap3 mobile-first?",
            options:["True","False","Can't say","May be"],
            answer:"True"
        },
        {
            question:"Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to provide a responsive fixed width container?",
            options:[".container-fixed",".container-fluid",".container","All of the above"],
            answer:" .container"
        },
        {
            question:"Which of the following class in bootstrap is used to create a big box for calling extra attention?",
            options:["box","container","container-fluid","jumbotron"],
            answer:".jumbotron"
        }
    ],
    JavaScript:[
        {
            question:"Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
            options:["Object-Oriented","Object-Based","Assembly-language","High-level"],
            answer:"Object-Based"
        },
        {
            question:"Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
            options:["Alternative to if-else","Switch statement","If-then-else statement","immediate if"],
            answer:"immediate if"
        },
        {
           question:" The function and var are known as:",
           options:["Keywords","Data types","Declaration statements","Prototypes"],
           answer:"Declaration statements"
        },
        {
            question:"When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
            options:["Shows a warning","Prompts to complete the statement" ,"Throws an error","Ignores the statements"],
            answer:"Ignores the statements"
        }
    ]
}
